{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Security Monitoring Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/40138/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40138,"taskName":"Alarm or Security System - Monitor","taskDescription":"Monitor Alarms from Security System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Security Monitoring Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1101,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Alarm Security System burglar protection","textMessagingName":"Alarm Monitor","rolloverLongDesc":"In most areas, when a security alarm sounds, it does not immediately call the police, but rather notifies an alarm monitoring service. After confirming that it is not a false alarm, the service contacts the police or anyone else as directed by the owner. This is a specialized service. One monitoring service may work with many security companies.","rolloverShortDesc":"Monitoring service that responds to alarms.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Monitor Alarms from Security System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Security \u0026 Alarm System Monitoring \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Alarm System Monitor","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Alarm or Security System - Monitor","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security System Project","urlName":"Alarm-or-Security-System-Monitor","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Home Security Monitoring Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews, Costs","searchKeywords":"Alarm,Security,System,burglar,protection,surveillance,sercuirty,secure,safe,protect,alarms,Monitor","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":449,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40138/":{"taskOID":40138,"originalTaskOID":40138,"setID":449,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4457,"questionDisplayText":"How System Was Acquired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How did you acquire your existing security system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bought it and had it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and had it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1090,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bought it and installed it myself","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and installed it myself","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3372,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"It was in the house when I moved in","answerDisplayText":"It was in the house when I moved in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"It is leased","answerDisplayText":"It is leased","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4459,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features currently in your security system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke detectors","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2642,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6688,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video","answerDisplayText":"Video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4460,"questionDisplayText":"Changes needed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want to make any changes to your current system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4457,"questionDisplayText":"How System Was Acquired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How did you acquire your existing security system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bought it and had it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and had it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1090,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bought it and installed it myself","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and installed it myself","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3372,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"It was in the house when I moved in","answerDisplayText":"It was in the house when I moved in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"It is leased","answerDisplayText":"It is leased","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bought it and had it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and had it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1090,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bought it and installed it myself","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and installed it myself","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","answerDisplayText":"Bought it and need to get it installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3372,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"It was in the house when I moved in","answerDisplayText":"It was in the house when I moved in","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3371,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"It is leased","answerDisplayText":"It is leased","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4459,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features currently in your security system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke detectors","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2642,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6688,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video","answerDisplayText":"Video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2468,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke detectors","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2642,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6688,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video","answerDisplayText":"Video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4460,"questionDisplayText":"Changes needed?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want to make any changes to your current system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}